Welcome to SubFlix!
SubFlix වෙත සාදරයෙන් පිළිගනිමු!
This is a sample subtitle file
for testing the extension.
මෙය දිගුව පරීක්ෂා කිරීම සඳහා
නියැදි උපශීර්ෂ ගොනුවකි.
You can adjust the timing
using the control buttons.
ඔබට පාලන බොත්තම් භාවිතා කරමින්
කාලය සකස් කළ හැක.
Try changing the font size,
background, and text color!
SubFlix supports Unicode characters:
العربية • 中文 • 日本語 • 한글
Multi-line subtitles work perfectly.
Line breaks are preserved.
Like this!
කර්තෘ: ඔබේ නම
Subtitle by: Your Name
Keyboard shortcuts:
Ctrl+Shift+S to toggle
Ctrl+← / Ctrl+→
to adjust timing quickly
Perfect for watching content
in unsupported languages!
අසমත් භාෂාවලින් අන්තර්ගතය නැරඹීමට
හොඳ මෙවලමකි!
Settings are automatically saved
and persisted.
Per-video delay memory keeps
your timing adjustments.
Test with different positions:
Top, Middle, or Bottom
Adjust background opacity
for better readability.
Enable shadows for text
that pops on any background!
Export your settings
to share or backup.
Import settings
from a JSON file.
Very long subtitle lines will automatically wrap to the next line and maintain proper formatting even with extended text content that would normally exceed the display width.
Special characters work too:
™ © ® ℗ ♪ ♫ ☺ ❤
Emojis are supported:
😀 🎬 📺 🎭 🎪
This extension is open source!
Contribute on GitHub.
Thank you for using SubFlix!
SubFlix භාවිතා කිරීම සඳහා ස්තූතියි!
Enjoy your viewing experience
with custom subtitles!
End of sample subtitles.
නියැදි උපශීර්ෂ අවසානය.